Guide to the Stephen Vincent Benét and Rosemary Benét Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Personal Papers, 1843-1962; Series VI; 19.94; 28 boxes
  - Family Papers
    - Benét, William Rose
      - Reproduction of drawing, undated (Box 137 (Oversize), Folder 3280)
    - Carr, Rachel H.
      - Carr family history material, 1931-1943, undated (Box 99, Folder 2882)
      - Diagram relating to property lines, undated (Box 146 (Bsd))
      - Prescription letterhead, undated (Box 99, Folder 2883)
      - Printed ephemera, 1928, 1930 (Box 99, Folder 2884)
    - Carr, Thomas
      - Clippings, 1900, undated (Box 99, Folder 2885)
      - Financial records, 1888-1923, undated (Box 99, Folder 2886-2887)
      - Last will and testament, 1923 May 14 (Box 99, Folder 2888)
      - Legal and other records, 1894–1915 (Box 99, Folder 2889)
      - Letters of introduction, 1879–1880 (Box 99, Folder 2890)
      - Plant specimens, undated (Box 99, Folder 2891)
      - Printed ephemera, 1878-190[?], undated (Box 99, Folder 2892)
      - Probate record, undated (Box 99, Folder 2893)
      - "Utility of Naval Offices", undated (Box 99, Folder 2894)
    - Mahon family
      - Miscellaneous papers, 1919, undated (Box 99, Folder 2895)
    - Rose family
      - Genealogical material, undated (Box 99, Folder 2896)
    - Walker, Amanda (Helms)
      - Death announcement, 1856 September 4 (Box 137 (Oversize), Folder 3281)
  - Financial and Legal Records
    - Cancelled Checks
      - Bank of Italy, 1930 (Box 100, Folder 2897)
      - Clinton National Bank, 1937–1938 (Box 100, Folder 2898)
      - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1929–1936 (Box 100, Folder 2899)
      - National City Bank of New York, 1929–1935 (Box 100, Folder 2900-2906)
      - National City Bank of New York, 1936–1943 (Box 101, Folder 2907-2911)
      - Wakefield Trust Company, 1930–1935 (Box 101, Folder 2912-2917)
    - Contracts
      - Art Cinema Corporation, 1929 November 29 (Box 102, Folder 2918)
      - Associated Hospital Service of New York, 1939 September 1 (Box 102, Folder 2919)
      - C. V. Whitney Pictures, 1955 February 9 (Box 102, Folder 2920)
      - Countryman Press, 1939 December 17 (Box 102, Folder 2921)
      - Doubleday, Doran & Company, 1927, 1929 (Box 102, Folder 2922)
      - Doubleday, Doran & Company, 1927 August 25 (Box 137 (Oversize), Folder 3282)
      - Douglas Moore, 1941 August [11?] (Box 102, Folder 2923)
      - E. C. Schirmer Music Company, 1937 January 7 (Box 102, Folder 2924)
      - Farrar & Rinehart, 1933–1944 (Box 102, Folder 2925)
      - First National Pictures, Inc., 1924 September 5 (Box 102, Folder 2926)
      - Heinemann (Firm), 1926–1937 (Box 102, Folder 2927)
      - Metro-Goldwyn-Mayer, 1951–1952 (Box 102, Folder 2928)
      - Overseas Editions, Inc., 1944 November (Box 102, Folder 2929)
      - Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation, 1939 May 9 (Box 102, Folder 2930)
    - Royalty Statements
      - Boosey Hawkes (Firm), 1941 (Box 102, Folder 2931)
      - Brandt & Brandt, 1924–1961 (Box 102, Folder 2932-2937)
      - Doubleday, Doran & Company, 1926–1938 (Box 102, Folder 2938-2939)
      - Dramatists Play Service, 1941 July 25 (Box 102, Folder 2940)
      - E. C. Schirmer Music Company, 1936 June 5 (Box 102, Folder 2941)
      - Farrar & Rinehart, 1931–1941 (Box 102, Folder 2942-2943)
      - Heinemann (Firm), 1927–1940 (Box 103, Folder 2944)
      - Henry Holt, 1927-1942, undated (Box 103, Folder 2945)
      - Rinehart Company, Inc., 1953 (Box 103, Folder 2946)
    - Other Records
      - Bank statements and receipts, 1928-1943, undated (Box 103, Folder 2947)
      - Certificate of registration of an automobile, 1931–1933 (Box 103, Folder 2948)
      - Check stubs, 1936-1947, undated (Box 103, Folder 2949)
      - Check and transaction booklets, 1925-1930, undated (Box 103, Folder 2950)
      - "Death Letter", undated (Box 103, Folder 2951)
      - "Estate of Stephen Vincent Benet", [1943?] (Box 103, Folder 2952)
      - Estate of Mary Carr, 1936 (Box 103, Folder 2953)
      - Income taxes, 1924-1942, undated (Box 103, Folder 2954-2964)
      - Income taxes, 1929–1936 (Box 137 (Oversize), Folder 3283)
      - Insurance documents, 1933–1941 (Box 103, Folder 2965)
      - Invoices and receipts, 1924-1959, undated (Box 103, Folder 2966)
      - Lease of apartment, 1930 September 22 (Box 103, Folder 2967)
  - Photographs
    - Albums
      - Album [#1], 1911, undated (Box 104, Folder 2968)
      - Album [#2], 1905-[circa 1911] (Box 105, Folder 2969)
      - Album [#3], 1901-1928, undated (Box 106, Folder 2970)
      - Album [#4], 1929, undated (Box 107, Folder 2971)
    - People
      - Benét children and family, undated (Box 108, Folder 2972)
      - Benét, Estanislada Frances, undated (Box 108, Folder 2973)
      - Benét, Isabel, undated (Box 108, Folder 2974)
      - Benét, Juana Hernandez, [circa 1880], undated (Box 108, Folder 2975)
      - Benét, Laura Walker, 1880, 1897 (Box 108, Folder 2976)
      - Benét, Pedro, undated (Box 108, Folder 2977)
      - Benét, Rachel, [1930s] (Box 108, Folder 2978)
      - Benét, Rosemary, [circa 1903]-1928 (Box 108, Folder 2979)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1922-1923, undated (Box 108, Folder 2980)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent, undated (Box 137 (Oversize), Folder 3284)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent (with Rosemant Benét), 1921-[1928], undated (Box 108, Folder 2981)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent (with family), 1926, undated (Box 108, Folder 2982)
      - Benét, Stephen Vincent (with family), undated (Box 137 (Oversize), Folder 3285)
      - Carr, [Rosa?], undated (Box 108, Folder 2983)
      - Carr, Thomas, undated (Box 108, Folder 2984)
      - Dunn, Laura (Benét), undated (Box 108, Folder 2985)
      - Others, undated (Box 108, Folder 2986)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 108, Folder 2987)
    - Photographs Removed from Albums
      - Album [#1], 1907-1914, undated (Box 108, Folder 2988)
      - Album [#2], 1905-[circa 1911] (Box 108, Folder 2989)
      - Album [#3], 1901-1928, undated (Box 108, Folder 2990-2991)
      - Album [#3], undated (Box 137 (Oversize), Folder 3286)
      - Album [#4], 1929, undated (Box 108, Folder 2992-2995)
    - Places
      - Augusta, Georgia, 1912 (Box 108, Folder 2996)
      - Home of Pedro Benét, St. George Street, St. Augustine, Florida, undated (Box 108, Folder 2997)
      - Ordnance Training Camp, Augusta Georgia, undated (Box 108, Folder 2998)
      - Tombstones of Benét family members, 1938, undated (Box 108, Folder 2999)
      - "Walker Homestead," Richmond, Kentucky, 1940, undated (Box 108, Folder 3000)
    - Other
      - Autograph of Pedro Benét, undated (Box 108, Folder 3001)
  - Rosemary Benét Material
    - Accounting book, [1922?] (Box 109, Folder 3002)
    - Addresses, undated (Box 109, Folder 3003)
    - Autograph manuscript notes, undated (Box 109, Folder 3004-3004a)
    - Biographical sketch, undated (Box 109, Folder 3005)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club material, 1943-1958, undated (Box 109, Folder 3006-3010)
    - Calendars, 1932–1937 (Box 110, Folder 3011)
    - Calendars, 1938–1942 (Box 111, Folder 3012)
    - Calendars, 1942–1960 (Box 112, Folder 3013)
    - Calling cards, undated (Box 113, Folder 3014)
    - "Carnet de bébé", [1920s] (Box 113, Folder 3015)
    - Certificate, 1954 June 9 (Box 113, Folder 3016)
    - Clippings, 1918-1940, undated (Box 113, Folder 3017)
    - Clippings, 1918-1920, undated (Box 137 (Oversize), Folder 3287)
    - The Cosmopolitan Club material, 1933-1955, undated (Box 113, Folder 3018-3019)
    - Finch College material, 1945–1951 (Box 113, Folder 3020)
    - "Journal for Stephen", 1943 (Box 113, Folder 3021)
    - Lease, 1944 May 22 (Box 113, Folder 3022)
    - Medical records, undated (Box 113, Folder 3023)
    - New York Society Library material, 1959 (Box 113, Folder 3024)
    - Notebook, undated (Box 113, Folder 3025)
    - Printed ephemera, 1919-1946, undated (Box 113, Folder 3026)
    - Printed ephemera, 1938 June 3 (Box 137 (Oversize), Folder 3288)
    - Ribbon, undated (Box 113, Folder 3027)
    - School records, 1906–1917 (Box 113, Folder 3028)
    - Scrapbook, 1899-1921,undated (Box 113, Folder 3029-3030)
    - Shipping label, undated (Box 113, Folder 3031)
  - Other Papers
    - Academy of American Poets, 1938-1962, undated (Box 113, Folder 3032-3034)
    - Academy of American Poets, 1938-1962, undated (Box 114, Folder 3035-3039)
    - Addresses, undated (Box 114, Folder 3040)
    - "Astrology", [1923-1935?], undated (Box 114, Folder 3041)
    - Autographs, undated (Box 114, Folder 3042)
    - Empty folder (Box 114, Folder 3043)
    - Bibliographical notes, undated (Box 114, Folder 3044)
    - Biographical information, 1947, undated (Box 114, Folder 3045-3046)
    - Diaries, 1932–1935 (Box 114, Folder 3047-3050)
    - Diaries, 1936–1940 (Box 115, Folder 3051-3055)
    - Diaries, 1941–1943 (Box 116, Folder 3056-3058)
    - Diary excerpts, undated (Box 116, Folder 3059)
    - Drawings and illustrations, undated (Box 116, Folder 3060)
    - Drawings and illustrations, undated (Box 137 (Oversize), Folder 3289)
    - Fabric, undated (Box 116, Folder 3061)
    - Kerchief for Socialist Party, [circa 1930s] (Box 137 (Oversize), Folder 3290)
    - "Life History Album", 1884–1914 (Box 116, Folder 3062)
    - Lists, 1943, undated (Box 116, Folder 3063-3064)
    - Lock of hair, undated (Box 116, Folder 3065)
    - Manuscript notes and fragments, undated (Box 116, Folder 3066)
    - Material relating to wedding, 1912-1923, undated (Box 117, Folder 3067)
    - New York Public Library call slip, undated (Box 117, Folder 3068)
    - Notebooks, undated (Box 117, Folder 3069-3080a)
    - Notebooks, undated (Box 118, Folder 3081-3092)
    - Notebooks, undated (Box 119, Folder 3093)
    - Printed ephemera removed from photograph album [#3], 1930, undated (Box 119, Folder 3094)
    - Printed ephemera removed from photograph album [#3], 1930, undated (Box 137 (Oversize), Folder 3291)
    - Printed ephemera removed from photograph album [#4], 1930-1941, undated (Box 119, Folder 3095)
    - Printed ephemera removed from photograph album [#4], 1932-1941, undated (Box 137 (Oversize), Folder 3292)
    - Ration books, [1940s] (Box 119, Folder 3096)
    - Records relating to Stephen Vincent Benét's birth, 1919 (Box 119, Folder 3097)
    - School records, 1910–1919 (Box 119, Folder 3098)
    - Scrapbook (Box 120, Folder 3099)
    - "Strong box" for diaries, undated (Box 121, Folder 3100)
    - Wood and printing blocks, undated (Box 122, Folder 3101)
    - Other Material, undated (Box 122, Folder 3102)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, Series VII
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - In Series I - Series III (Box 138, Folder 3293-3395)
  - In Series III (Box 139, Folder 3396-3408)
  - In Series III (Box 140, Folder 3409-3449)
  - In Series III (Box 141, Folder 3450-3492)
  - In Series III, Series VI (Box 142, Folder 3493-3517)
  - In Series III, Series V (Box 143 (Oversize), Folder 3518-3521)